

# **ADITI MATHUR**

Gurgaon, Haryana India Aditimathur0810@gmail.com / +91-7065263707

#### **PROFILES**

linkedin.com/in/aditimathur98

#### CAREER OBJECTIVE

A learning enthusiast, seeking job at a reputed organization to utilize expertise in development and research. Coming with well-honed skills in computer science, and 3+ years of experience as a full stack engineer in addition to excellent communication skills.

# CERTIFICATION

## 1. Professional Certificate Program in Blockchain : IIT Kanpur - Simplilearn Certified - 2023

- Fundamentals of Blockchain
- Blockchain Applications And Architecture
- Capstone Project- Professional Certificate Program in Blockchain
- Academic Masterclass-Professional Certificate Program in Blockchain- IIT kanpur

## 2.Other Certifications

- Upgrad Full Stack Development (2019-20)
- Test Dome Python (2020)
- Triplebyte Backend Engineer Advanced Certification (2022)

## **EXPERIENCE**

# Sr. Software Engineer / Authbridge Pvt. Ltd - India

09/2022 - Current

- Started as a software engineer responsible for in-house CRM product named 'Smart' built on cakePHP and python with external integrations. Managed deployments and introduced CI/CD for the project.
- Worked in Bridge India's largest B2B employment verification portal, APIs for report management and GST process download handled by working closely with Finance and Operations.
- Presently working with iBridge Candidate Verification portal, handling APIs for verification requirements of client sub products.

# Software Developer / Real Time Data Services Pvt. Ltd - India

01/2020 - 08/2022

- Worked in Ace Cloud Hosting's payment portal, product development and design for the project, focus on implementation of restful APIs
  of payment gateways. Responsible for CRM integration for contact management. Presented with company's innovation award for the
  same
- Worked with cloud telephony product Servetel and later Tata acquired product Smartflo. Responsible for permission module and analytical reports.
- Working presently in Dialer (Tata Smartflo) responsible for overall development and upkeep of the agent based smart telephony
  product. Experienced in NodeJS, Angular, MongoDB, SQL.
- Presented with Going extra mile award for Agent scripting and DND modules.
- Responsible for schedule call automation strategy for dialing and scripting.

### Software Developer Intern / Icubeswire Technologies Pvt Ltd

06/2019 - 07/2019

Gained knowledge of basic web technologies – HTML, CSS, JS, PHP.

- Performed security analytics over few client-based products for the company.
- Generated reports for business analytics by attending marketing and client meetings

## **EDUCATION**

Professional Certificate Program: Blockchain 2023

IIT Kanpur - Certified

Bachelor of Technology: CSE 2020

School of Engineering & Technology - Ansal University | CGPA 8.4

Intermediate 2016

Rotary Public School - Percentage: 81.2%

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Programming Languages: C/C++, Python, PHP

• Web Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Angular

(Laravel, Cake), NodeJS • Tools : Git, Postman, Jira

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Languages: English & Hindi.

Database: SQL, MongoDB

• Soft Skills: Time Management, Team player, Client interaction, public speaking, presentation skills.